I don't know how in this September 5th, 2025, the year of the old gods and the new, I don't know how y'all are still talking about election cycles.
I don't know how y'all are still talking about we wouldn't have this if we didn't have Kamala.
There's no way that you can understand the concept of a cycle, which is something that starts here and then comes back here and think that it resets every time.
Um, it's not, it's not practical. It's not logical. Right. And so when we understand cycles, we have to understand that there's going to be shifts.
There's going to be ways that the landscape is affected every time. Right. So like, think about when you walk in a circle, when you walk in a circle in the same place, you end up creating a track.
You displace what's there. You disrupt what's there. Unless you are actively correcting as you go.
But the United States does not do that. There is no correcting as we go.
So when we talk about the concept of election cycles and we talk about how did that pay Deborah, we can very consciously see that it would never in any shape or form take one election cycle to get us to a dictatorial fascist state.
The concept of that is, is literally nonsensical. It is impractical to believe that one election cycle would have saved us from such a thing.
Because in order for such a thing to happen, there had to be much disruption to clear a path.
And so it becomes our responsibility to study the cycles that came before and how those paths were cleared and to also do the work of restoring.
Understanding that in the same way that a skater very rarely is able to spin in the same place.
It's like when you watch them do those crazy dope spins, you'll see that they shift, even if it's a little, because the goal is to not shift.
But even if they shift a little, it's going to move.
And in that moving, in that shifting, you will see possibility for change in the worst, but in the best ways as well.